[music]
>> Good morning, guys, and welcome to a new
vlog. I'm so happy to see you. I am on
my way to go have a little cozy
breakfast at this place in Copenhagen
called Hans. I just have to bring you
guys along because it is truly my
favorite spot in Copenhagen. They have a
few locations, but this is the place
where you can have the best in
Copenhagen. I haven't been like the
biggest fan of BMOs, if I'm being
honest, because usually the cafes in
Copenhagen don't offer jam with the bun,
and I feel like it's just a little bit
dry and salty, and without the jam, it's
not that good. But let me tell you, this
place truly makes the best one. I
literally think about this breakfast
every single morning.
have a book that I want to finish today,
My Brilliant Friend by Elena Ferrante.
Oh my goodness, guys. I think this might
be one of my all-time favorite books,
and I was not expecting that when I
started reading it, because it took me a
while to get into it. So it follows
these two girls who are living in
Naples, and it follows their friendship
throughout four books. So this is the
first book, and it starts pretty early
when they're quite young, and I just
wasn't sure if I was going to love it,
even though the writing from the
beginning was so, so beautiful, but I
just wasn't really like, oh my goodness,
I'm going to love this. I continued
reading it even though I was a little
bit confused about all of the different
characters, but I really love also that,
you know, it is an Italian story that is
translated to English, but it just has
these, you know, Italian words, and
Italian names, Italian locations, and I
feel like I've been transported to Italy
and I'm in Naples, and it's honestly
just a really, really beautiful book.
Yesterday, I got a little bit ahead of
myself.
I started watching the TV adaptation of
this book series, and oh my goodness, it
was really something good. I'm so picky
when it comes to TV shows and movies. I
really love, you know, older movies and
older TV shows because, as you've
probably seen like the Netflix filter, I
watched Devil Wears Prada and my last
vlog, and I actually didn't give you
guys my thoughts on the movie, but I did
not like it at all. Uh it had this
Netflix filter. Everything was just so
picture perfect, the lighting, the
audio, everything kind of just staged.
But I feel like in the older days or
like, you know, older films, older TV
shows, they still have that natural
element to it. I mean, you don't even
have to go that far. I think Breaking
Bad, we were currently watching uh
Sopranos, which is quite funny because
they are also like Italian-Americans.
So, some of these names, I'm like
recognizing and some of the slangs and
stuff that they're using. Okay, anyways,
I'm going way ahead of myself. What why
did I start talking about this? But
yeah, the TV show, My Brilliant Friend,
I only watched the first episode. So,
it's an HBO series, but it's in Italian
and it's filmed in Italy, I believe, and
I think all of the actors are Italian.
And it's just so raw and it's so so
beautiful. I immediately like I knew
that I was going to love it. It is
identical to the book. I feel like every
scene has been literally the same as the
book. Uh, which is really cool because
that's not often times when, you know,
they make movies or TV shows from books.
But this one,
wow, I was blown away and I'm excited to
watch more and finish this one. And
yeah, I'm going to take myself on a cozy
morning date. And miss Matilda
is a little sleepy head.
My little cutie.
But I thought maybe I could show you
guys what I'm going to wear. So, my hair
is a little bit oily today, so I just
threw on
this headband.
This is actually Hedi's back.
But I'm going to steal it today and I'm
wearing these pleated pants,
my flip-flops, and this gray V-neck.
Me.
>> We're going to find another place so we
can
sit in the sun while
we read because the other place was in
the shadow. It's a little bit cold, but
in the sun
it's so nice. Yeah, I also brought
Helge's book because he was out and
about and he was maybe going to meet me
and he is reading
You're almost finished
as well.
>> Oof, it's been what?
A year or something since
>> No, not a not a year, but it's taken you
a while. You also read to quite a few
books like in between. You had to take
some breaks. I'm not sure if I'm going
to read it.
>> [music]
>> We found a little spot here
where we can sit
and read by the lake.
And there's a little duck over there.
Hello.
>> [music]
>> Well, guys
we finished.
Oh, and it's been such a lovely day.
And the sun is just
beaming and there are lots of boats and
kayaks passing by here. So wholesome,
but we actually want to go home now
because
we recently got a delivery. It's a
poster and a frame that we are going to
put in our living room and we haven't
unboxed it yet because I really wanted
to film the process with you guys. So I
think we're going to go home now and
>> Unbox it.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
>> [music]
[music]
>> We just got home and
>> [clears throat]
>> she is lying so funny.
Look at her, Mata. Hi. Hello.
Cutiepie. We did a little
shopping before heading home. I also
went to the store to pick up some
necessities while we're unboxing the
poster and the frame, but we also went
to this store that we bypassed and we
got some coconut oil,
slap av tea, which means like relaxing
tea, and we bought toothbrushes. I
haven't bought these before, but I
wanted to try them because it's like
made from plants and they looked pretty
good, so. And I really wanted to buy
high-quality olive oil. I mean, this one
is organic and it's extra virgin olive
oil, but I'm not sure if it's just like
the pure best olive oil that you can
like drink in the morning. I really want
to buy that type of olive oil where you
can just like sip on it with some lemon
juice. I don't know if you guys have
seen that, but olive oil like so good
for you, but I mean, we're just going to
try this one out and see how it is. And
yeah, we also wanted to try
this water kefir, ginger and lemon. I
think it's a little bit like kombucha. I
actually don't know the difference.
I love everything ginger and lemon. Mm.
Oh my.
Yum. It's not sweet at all.
It's more like sparkling water with a
little bit of ginger and lemon. It's not
like ginger ale, but
really refreshing.
Matilda is
always so cuddly when we get home. When
she's been alone and then she's craving
some cuddles and scratches
and kisses.
Oh.
Well, oh well.
>> It's cute.
>> It's so big.
I believe the poster is up here.
And then this here is like this dark
wood frame. This is from a Danish brand
called Pelikan. They kindly gifted us
this piece and I'm so excited to style
it in our apartment. I don't know if we
should have it here, above the cabinet,
or above the sofa, but let's see.
By the way, this poster is called Cheers
My Friend. I was in between a couple of
artworks from this German artist called
Hanne Müller. I think all of them are
absolutely beautiful, but I felt like
this one would just suit this living
room really nicely.
Ta-da!
Oh my goodness. It's so stunning.
Wow.
>> Well, guys, what do you think? I am in
love. It is even bigger than I imagined.
I love big artworks. I feel like it just
really elevates every space. So, I'm so
happy with this one. We haven't hung it
up just yet because we're still debating
if we should keep it above the cabinet
or above the sofa. Uh and then we need
to borrow a drilling machine from our
friend. So, we're not going to hang it
up today, but I feel like the living
room just upgraded immediately. So, I'm
really really happy.
We just got ready because we're meeting
our friends for dinner. And I'm pretty
much wearing the same outfit as I did
today, but I added this leather blazer
and my loafers because it can get pretty
cold when sets. I don't know where we're
going to go for dinner, but
probably going to sit somewhere
>> [music]
>> in the sun.
>> We are back home. It was really cozy
evening. We had some pizzas
and I actually had a cheeseburger. And
we just sat there in the sun. Yeah, I
took a shower because I was so cold and
my hair was dirty. And I love taking a
shower before I go to bed. Not
necessarily like soaking wet, but I feel
like my hair gets a little bit more wavy
in the morning. Hey, guys. I just
realized that we bought something
earlier this week.
>> [snorts]
>> I am so excited. I had forgotten, but we
bought Ben & Jerry's Cookie Dough
earlier this week because it was on sale
and we thought we could like have a
movie night and have Ben & Jerry's. So,
we're going to watch The Drama with
Zendaya and Robert Pattinson. I am so
excited to watch it. I think I'm going
to love it. I absolutely adore the
actors and it's an A24 movie. I usually
love all of their movies, so I'm quite
excited. I'll tell you guys tomorrow
what I think about it. If there's one
thing that Matilda loves, it's Ben &
Jerry's. And it's crazy because she
recognizes the packaging even. She is so
smart.
We usually let her lick the top thingy,
but never if we buy the Half Baked one
because that one has chocolate. You
know, it's just like tiny bit of ice
cream. Um,
I'm just waiting for her to jump up.
She's like looking at me over here.
>> [laughter]
>> Just wait. She's going to come.
I'm honestly shocked that Oh, there she
is.
Hello. And she's going to come very
close.
Mhm.
Mhm. That is good. There she is.
>> [laughter]
>> She's like [snorts] my bestie, you know.
Hey.
Aw, you are such a cutie pie.
Mhm, [snorts]
Ben & Jerry, yummy.
Mhm, yummy num.
>> [snorts]
[music]
>> Good morning. I am currently making my
homemade granola. I haven't made it in a
while and I'm just really excited to be
making it again because I bought this
yogurt at the farmers' market and I
really wanted to make like homemade
granola.
I met [snorts] the people that are the
owners of this farm and they were
genuinely like the sweetest people and
they told me all about their farm and it
was really inspiring. So, honestly, I
want to go more often to the farmers'
market and buy like good products and
produce. So, I got
beef bone broth that I wanted to try
out. You guys know I love bone broth,
but it can be quite time-consuming to
make it, so it's nice to be able to buy
it at the farmers' market and then, of
course,
some eggs.
And then, I discovered this kombucha. I
just thought it [snorts] looked really
beautiful. I actually didn't get to try
it, but since Helg and I don't drink
alcohol, I thought this could be fun to
like bring to the park or something when
you're having a little picnic. This is
probably going to be so so tasty. Okay,
but I'm going to make my delicious
granola now. And honestly guys, if
you're still buying granola at the
store, you are missing out because
homemade granola is way better and it's
so nice because you can basically just
throw in whatever you have at home. So,
I'm going to put some almonds, walnuts,
pumpkin seeds, flax seeds, coconut
flakes. I'm just going to put a bunch of
stuff in there and it's
delish.
>> [snorts]
>> I'm going to be a bit bougie, so I'm
going to add some vanilla bean into the
coconut oil. It's going to taste so
good.
>> [music]
[music]
>> How did you just make me some iced
coffee? We're going to go for a walk
with our stepson. They go. We've started
calling him our stepson. It's the dog
that we've been dog sitting. Eh, but
yeah, we've been walking him quite a bit
and he is he is so special. I adore him.
But yeah, I wanted to tell you guys my
thoughts on the drama. Oh my goodness,
it was very unexpected. I had no clue
what the movie was about. Eh, I hadn't
seen the trailer, which I think made it
even more fun for me because it was just
quite disturbing this movie, but I just
really love A24. They just love to
surprise you with like the most
unexpected things happening. I don't
know, I thought this movie was going to
be about like them getting married and
just like maybe some relationship
complications or something. Eh, but
little did I know.
I rated the movie four out of five on my
letterboxd. I honestly really enjoyed
it. I kind of like movies that are weird
and just kind of get under your skin in
a way. They're just a little bit
unexpected. This one was definitely
quite disturbing, but yeah, I would
highly recommend watching it. I really
enjoyed the cinematography. I loved
Robert Pattinson and Zendaya and the
overall vibe, but it is kind of messed
up, so just be prepared.
But anyways, it's going to be nice with
a little walk. I've been sorting out
some stuff and we haven't really gone
outside. So, we're going to go for a
little walk. I feel like I'm just so
like tired in the face.
Maybe it's because my eyelashes are just
flat. It just makes me a little bit
sleepy. I don't know. [snorts]
Let's go.
Hi. Wow.
>> [laughter]
>> I recently [music] got this
hoodie, and it says 77. And Helgi just
told me it's uh his football jersey
number that he used to like wear his
whole childhood. [music]
>> And my basketball jersey as well.
>> Oh my gosh. So, it's like it's even more
special to me now.
>> [music]
[music]